Impel Down, a living hell buried beneath the waves where the world's most notorious prisoners are held.
Yet despite being history's most heavily fortified prison, it has been breached by an upstart pirate named Straw Hat Luffy.
He hopes to free his brother Fire Fist Ace, who is condemned to be executed.
However, he is not the only one to make his way through the prison's iron defenses.
Another breach occurred 20 years before.
The culprit was the first and only man to successfully break out of the legendary prison and see the light of day again.
Unbelievable.
That damned lunatic cut off his own legs to escape.
And with this astonishing feat, he wrote his name in the pages of history.
Captain of the dreaded flying pirates, Shiki the Golden Lion.
These events transpired only a matter of days before Luffy and the Straw Hat Pirates faced Shiki himself in battle.
A special presentation related to the movie. A Gold Lion's Ambition on the Move.
Captain, seen your call?
Si, what is it?
There's a call. I think it's from the Big Boss Shiki's people.
About time. Sure kept us waiting. Bring me the transponder snail.
Jaser, right away.
You hear that, Big Bro? We might get to team up with Shiki's crew.
If this pans out, we'll be in the Grande Leagues. Just you wait.
Bye.
Hey, Big Bro, are those happy tears?
Sad tears, the saddest hermano cold.
I'm filled with a beautiful sorrow, and we...
If Senor Siki succeeds in the implementation of his odious machinations,
the world will be drowned in a tidal wave of despair.
Si, when I imagine the thousands of wailing voices crying out in agony,
I feel simply, overwhelmingly sad.
Sir, here's the Transwanderous Nail.
Good, put him through.
Am I speaking with the Captain of the Amigo Pirates, Captain Largo?
No, this is Vice Captain Colt, but I'm speaking on behalf of Captain Largo.
Very well. This call is to inform you that Captain Siki has decided to accept Mr. Largo into his assembly as our 51st Pirate Captain. Congratulations.
Well, of course.
However, there is one condition.
A mere formality that must be completed before you join.
Oh!
Un condition?
Still no bites.
Where are you fish?
Man, I'm hungry.
You don't say, cause you look pretty full to me.
Well, we have been eating giant banquets every night. Our stomach's expanded. And as a result, we need to eat more to fill them up.
Oh, I know. It's ridiculous how heavy my bones have gotten these past few days.
That is not how it works.
How's it going? Catch anything yet?
Not yet. Not even a nibble.
We're completely out of food, you know. Either you catch something or we don't eat.
What?
Yeah, what? I kept telling you guys we didn't have enough food to do banquets every damn night. But you had to party.
Is that what we did?
Yeah.
Bunch of gluttons.
Huh?
Oh, a bite! A bite! A bite! I caught a bite!
Oh, reel it in! Nicely cut, bro!
It's a big sucker!
Awesome! We're having a banquet tonight!
Fix that fish even if it kills you!
Banquets!
Hey, fellas! It's coming!
We might starve, but at least they're having fun.
Oh!
Here it comes!
What is that?
Huh?
That's not good!
It's a huge beetle!
A fish!
Banquet!
Awesome!
Huh?
Don't tell me.
It's a pirate ship?
Those evil bastards aren't landing here!
Boss, take them down!
It's coming back!
That thing is freaking enormous!
I want to ride on it!
What?
That's just nuts, Bluebeam!
Hey, who's up?
Let's catch it!
Ready?
Hold on!
Were you waiting for that?
I'm not letting that bug destroy our ship!
Shoot and go!
Earn!
Sit down!
cev...
Frankie's attack didn't even faze it...
But I'm so super!
I got this one guys!
Hehehe!
He-hey Geah
Hey, beetle, bring it on!
He knocked us away, that's crazy!
Not only is it gigantic, but it breathes fire.
Damn, that thing's gonna roast our ship to a crisp!
Luffy, are you okay up there?
It's super big, super strong, and it breathes fire.
It's the coolest thing ever!
Yeah, I get the feeling he's okay.
I got a plan! I'm gonna make him join our crew!
Wait, what?! Hang on, Luffy!
All right, big guy, you're gonna join...
Yeah, I got you now!
This can't be happening.
Looks like they're headed back this way.
Indeed.
In fact, it looks like they're headed straight for us!
Make a run for us!
Help!
Help me!
Really, Usopp?
Oh, come on, you damn idiot!
And now it's flying away.
What's wrong with those morons?
Hey, there's an island over there.
I'm guessing that's where the beetle came from.
Uh-oh!
Watch out, boss! Pull up!
We're gonna hit the wall!
Uh-oh!
Uh-ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Good luck getting away now, you giant beetle!
So, you gonna join my crew or what?
For what? I'd say yes if I were you.
Boss is with me!
And he'd rather die than become a pirate!
Okay, so now what?
I didn't even know there was an island out here.
You know what I want to know?
What the hell are they doing?
Yoko, what's wrong?
Be careful, stay back!
This guy's a pirate!
Wait, he's a pirate?
Have mercy on us!
Stop fighting back, you pirate scum!
If I'm not mistaken, you folks are from the Straw Hat Pirates, aren't you?
Yeah, that's us!
Oh man, you're right! I thought I recognized them!
Yeah, that guy's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
And him! That's the infamous black-legged Sanji!
Uh, is that?
Wait, who was that guy?
Oh, come on!
Let me go! That jerk tried to take Boss away from me!
I'll bite him to death!
Yoko, calm down!
Shut up and let me at him!
Who in the hell are these people?
That really hurt!
Come on, I didn't know you were that Beetle's owner!
What owner?
He's my friend!
Nobody owns Boss!
Your friend?
Really? You're already on someone else's team then?
Don't you think he'd be better off on a real crew?
No, he wouldn't! Because Boss and I are inseparable!
Okay, can't argue with that!
Here we go!
Hey! What are you doing to him?
Whoa!
He's free!
Sorry if I hurt you, big guy!
You don't think he could hurt Boss, do you?
What? I didn't mean it like that!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey!
These wounds are nothing more than a few scratches to Boss!
They'll all heal up while he's sleeping underground tonight!
Wow! That's pretty badass!
Oh yeah, you think that's cool?
Well, he's gonna molt tomorrow too!
He'll get even bigger and stronger than he is now!
Huh. I didn't think Beetles kept on molting after they were fully grown.
Boss isn't an ordinary Beetle.
He sheds his skin once a month no matter how large he gets.
So as big as he is, he's only gonna get bigger.
He's gonna be even stronger than he is now?
Sure is! What, do you wanna fight about it?
Yeah! That's cool!
Listen! I'll come back tomorrow and we'll try again!
Uh!
Then we'll know for sure which one of us is the strongest!
But that's just ridiculous!
Uh!
No!
Huh?
All right!
You better not chicken out on me then!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
If nothing else, the boy sure is spirited, isn't he?
Boss?
Watch your step!
Wow! This cave is so cavernous!
What's it used for?
Oh, this? It's an escape route.
From what?
Well, this cave is like a massive labyrinth if you don't know your way around, so it's the perfect strategy for outrunning marauding pirates.
We'd be hard pressed to find anyone more adept at running away than we are.
And that's something you're proud of?
That's the only way we can survive on the Grand Line.
We don't have a military.
And the island is so remote that the Navy basically treats us like we don't even exist, so we're on our own.
Hey, speaking of the Navy, I noticed that girl was dressed up like a Marine.
What's that all about?
She wears that hat and coat.
In memory of her father.
That man was as good as they come.
He refused to look the other way while we kept getting attacked, so he left his battalion and stayed on our island in order to protect us.
And when you said, in memory of?
It happened five long years ago.
The poor brave man took on a group of pirates all by himself, and he was killed.
And then three years later, Boss appeared out of nowhere as if this was his home.
Yoko was the first to find him.
They bonded right away.
And he quickly became the guardian angel of our island.
Truth be told, I get the impression that Boss's strength and bravery remind poor little Yoko of her father.
Are you sure it's all right for us to be here?
We are pirates.
A different class of pirate.
Now, here we are.
Whoa!
A windmill!
It's huge!
We're so high up!
Whoa!
I thought we were just going to get more rocks, but it's actually beautiful back here.
Well, then again, not to be rude, but there's not much of an architectural uniformity here.
It's interesting though.
You don't recognize the theme?
What?
I don't know.
We're so high up!
Whoa!
I thought we were just going to get more rocks, but it's actually beautiful back here.
Well, then again, not to be rude, but there's not much of an architectural uniformity here.
It's interesting though.
You don't recognize the theme?
It was a deserted island when we came here, so we worked hard to make all the buildings look just like they do.
The strange thing is that everyone who's landed here since has come from the same ocean, so our town is like a microcosm in a way.
So we'd like to welcome you, Straw Hats, to Consorn Island, home away from home for expatriates of the East Blue.
We like to call it Little East Blue.
Yay!
Wow!
I never dreamed we'd have the East Blue's most famous rookies show up on our shore.
Hey, Zoro.
You're from Frost Moon Village, right?
We've got a dojo just like the one you trained in.
You should come and check it out.
Really?
And you grew up on the Baratie, right Sanji?
We'd love to hear what you think of the food in our Baratie.
It's pretty good.
There's a Baratie here?
Anyone here from Syrup Village?
Let's see.
I think Luigia might be from there, actually.
Luigia?
Yeah, that's right.
She lives in the biggest mansion in town.
A mansion?
But the only mansion in Syrup Village is the one Kaya lives in.
Everybody thinks they're so great, but no shifty pirate's gonna trick me.
I swear it.
It's been a while.
Do you think they're okay?
Don't get so worked up, Chopper.
I'm sure they'll call us soon.
Yeah, I hope so.
You might want to think about building an insect cage for when they return, Frankie.
Hey, good idea.
I guess we're gonna need one if that thing's our new shipmate.
You see?
Click.
It's me, Usopp.
I need to talk to Nami.
Hey, Usopp.
It's Nami.
What's going on?
Did you guys catch it okay?
No, no, no.
Forget about that.
Will you shut up and calm down?
I can't hear her.
Look, how quickly do you think you could get over to where we are?
Huh?
There's a town right on the other side of the island.
Wait, give me the boat.
She's coming.
Hey, get easy, guys.
I said I'd ask her, didn't I?
I'm so confused.
Please, just get over here.
I'm begging you.
Wait, why, Usopp?
He hung up on me.
Why do they just want you to come?
I don't know.
Well, I guess I might as well see what they want.
You guys take care of the ship?
Yeah, you got it.
And there she goes.
Is this it?
It matches the description they gave.
Rock-bound and surrounded by reefs.
A natural barricade that can support your ships.
Well, that's easy.
No reefs are going to slow down this ship.
All right, it's time to go hunting, boys.
Let's grab the giant beetle that escaped from Shiki's hideout.
Now, are you ready to catch a bug?
See you!
The Straw Hats have landed on an island where settlers from the East Blue live.
Surrounded by familiar sights, they're suddenly reminded of home,
even in faraway waters.
However, the peaceful settlement is soon disrupted from an attack
by the Amigo Pirates.
On the next, One Piece,
with a special presentation related to the movie,
Little East Blue in Danger.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!